techanger.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy - TechAnger

This Privacy Policy governs the style during which TechAnger collects, uses, maintains and discloses info collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.techanger.com web site (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the positioning and every one merchandise and services offered by TechAnger.

**Personal identification info**

We might gather your personal identification info from Users during a style of ways that, including, however not restricted to, once Users visit our website, register on the positioning, purchase the report, reply to a survey, fill out a kind, and in reference to alternative activities, services, options or resources we tend to create obtainable on our website. Users is also asked for, as applicable, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our website anonymously. we’ll collect personal identification info from Users given that they voluntarily submit such info to America. Users will continuously refuse to produce in person identification info, except that it should stop them from partaking in bound website connected activities.

**Non-personal identification info**

We could collect non-personal identification info regarding Users whenever they move with our website. Non-personal identification info could embody the browser name, the kind of laptop and technical info regarding Users suggests that of affiliation to our website, like the software system and therefore the net service suppliers utilised and alternative similar info.

**Web browser cookies**

Our website could use “cookies” to reinforce User expertise. User’s application places cookies on their Winchester drive for record-keeping functions and typically to trace info regarding them. User could value more highly to set their application to refuse cookies, or to warn you once cookies area unit being sent. If they are doing therefore, note that some elements of the positioning might not perform properly.

**Google Analytics**

We have enforced Google Analytics Demographics and Interest news. Any info we tend to collect can solely be wont to improve our client service and our website. you’ll be able to opt-out of Google Analytics for show Advertising and customise Google show Network ads mistreatment the Ads Settings.

**How we tend to use collected info**

TechAnger could collect and use Users personal info for the subsequent purposes:

  * To enhance client service.

_Information you offer helps America reply to your client service requests and support desires additional expeditiously._

  * To change user expertise.

_We could use info within the mixture to know however our Users as a bunch use the services and resources provided on our website._

  * To enhance our website.

_We could use feedback you offer to enhance our merchandise and services._

  * To send periodic emails.

_We could use the e-mail address to retort to their inquiries, questions, and/or alternative requests._

  * How we tend to defend your info.

_We adopt applicable information assortment, storage and process practices and security measures to guard against unauthorized access, alteration, revealing or destruction of your personal info, username, password, dealing info and information keep on our website._

**Sharing your personal info**

We don’t sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification info to others. we tend to could share generic aggregative demographic info not coupled to any personal identification info relating to guests and users with our business partners, trusty affiliates and advertisers for the needs printed on top of.We could offer third party service suppliers to assist us operate our business and therefore the website or administer activities on our behalf, like causing out newsletters or surveys.

**Third party websites**

Users could notice advertising or alternative content on our website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and alternative third parties. we tend to don’t management the content or links that seem on these sites and don’t seem to be answerable for the practices used by websites coupled to or from our website. additionally, these sites or services, as well as their content and links, is also perpetually dynamic . These sites and services could have their own privacy policies and client service policies. Browsing and interaction on the other web site, as well as websites that have a link to our website, is subject thereto website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads showing on our website is also delivered to Users by advertising partners, and these advertisement agencies  set cookies. These cookies permit the ad server to acknowledge your laptop on every occasion they send you a web advert to compile non personal identification info regarding you or others United Nations agency use your laptop. This info permits ad networks to, among alternative things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe are of most interest to you. This privacy policy doesn’t cowl the utilization of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes to the current privacy policy**

TechAnger has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we’ll revise the updated date at rock bottom of this page. we tend to encourage Users to oftentimes check this page for any changes to remain wise to regarding however we tend to area unit serving to to guard the private info we tend to collect. You acknowledge and agree that it’s your responsibility to review this privacy policy sporadically and become tuned in to modifications.

**Your acceptance of those terms**

By surfing this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree with the our privacy polciy, tplease dhen on’t use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to the current policy are deemed your acceptance of these changes. Thank you.

**How you Contact Us?**

If you’ve got any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact America at:  
http://www.techanger.com  
Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh(UP), India  
aamir@techanger.com

You can additionally use our contact kind

This document was last updated on November sixteen, 2013
